SEAN JORDAN

503-960-9380 Portland, OR 97214
https://seanjordan3.github.io/
seanjordan3@gmail.com
https://linkedin.com/in/sean-jordan77/
https://github.com/seanjordan3

Summary

Driven professional with broad technical skill set. Excellent communicator experienced in interpreting and implementing client and staff visions of new websites. Known for ability to multi-task and juggle multiple pressing projects simultaneously, meeting all deadlines. Thrives in environments that constantly embrace new technologies.

Skills

- Programming Languages: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, LESS, Sass
- Operating Systems: Windows XP-10, Mac OS X
- IDE's: Visual Studio, Brackets
- WordPress

- Frameworks: Bootstrap3/4, jQuery
- Version Control: Github, Azure
- Agile/SCRUM methodologies and TFS
- · Responsive design principles

Experience

AUGUST 2019 - PRESENT

Prosper IT Consulting / Front-end Web Developer Intern

Portland, OR

- Worked with project managers to design user interactions in applications.
- Created successful websites that met requirements for objectives such as load speed and design
- Operated in an Agile-governed workplace to get the best use of team resources while achieving project goals.
- Utilized HTML/CSS, Javascript, Github and Visual Studio.
- Improved and designed new layouts to achieve usability and performance objectives.
- Working within the Agile/SCRUM methodologies, attending daily stand up meetings and working on a team with several developers.

JUNE 2014 - FEBRUARY 2019

Nicky USA / IT Support

Portland, OR

- Troubleshoot and resolve issues with software or hardware.
- Delivered an exceptional level of service to each customer by listening to concerns and answering questions.
- Provided onsite training.

- Oversaw various warehouse projects from conceptualization to completion.
- Proactively identified and solved complex problems impacting operations management and business direction.

Education

FEBRUARY 2019- AUGUST 2019

The Tech Academy

Portland, OR

- Studied over 300 hours of content, tutorials, articles, and projects.
- Completed courses covering Computer and Technology Basics, Overview of Software Development, Version Control, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and Project Management.
- Design and layout responsive web applications using Frontend Development.
- Worked using an Agile methodology and Scrum.
- Tech Degree in Web Development.

SEPTEMBER 2004- JUNE 2006

University of Utah Salt Lake City, UT Associates in Biology

Associate of Science in Biology, Minor in Chemistry ● GPA: 3.5